So this is your issue,
- that she chose me, not you.
- Yes.
Because if it were me,
I would never make her cry!
Don't you think
this is pointless?
Don't forget.
Jin Ho likes Joey.
You have every right
to be upset with me.
I hope you understand, Jin Ho.
I don't want to hurt you either.
Hurry up and find Jin Ho.
Remember, he saw me.
I'm sorry, brother-in-law.
Instead of helping them escape,
it looks like you only put them
in danger.
Someone saw Jin Ho's car
on the toll camera
in Sta. Monica.
Jin Ho! You okay?
Your wounds got infected!
Joey...
Jin Ho...
[FROGS CROAKING]
- [JIN HO GROANS SOFTLY]
- [ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Joey...
Jin Ho, did you drink?
You really drank!
Oh my gosh, Jin Ho!
What now?
You already took medicine,
then you still drank alcohol.
What's going to happen
to you now?
What is this?
Joey...
[SPEAKS IN KOREAN]
Huh?
What are you saying?
What is this? A K-drama?
Joey...
[SPEAKS IN KOREAN]
Huh?
[SPEAKING IN KOREAN]
Joahae.
What was that?
[ROMANTIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Joahae.
He won't fight Joey
because he knows I like her.
He's not like that.
Peter, that was before.
Things change, just like me.
You know...
I didn't even expect
that I would care this much
about Joey.
What?
What did you say?
Nothing.
Are you in love with Joey too?
Hmm?
Ah...
What does that joahae even mean?
Why don't you say it in English?
Hello?
What?
Answer me.
What do you mean
by care this much?
Weren't you the one
who hurt Joey?
Weren't you saying all sorts of
things to her too?
Because I thought that was what
I needed to do.
Needed to do it for what?
To keep her away from the
trouble.
So she wouldn't continue her
plan with Jin Ho.
I don't want her getting hurt
because of me.
Seriously!
You're a journalist,
yet you let your emotions get
the better of you!
You should make sure first!
Oh, I'm sure now.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
So once we find her,
I won't waste a second.
Peter, I'm going to tell her
what I truly feel for her.
- You see.
- [SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
You got high from the alcohol
and the medicine you took.
This is your fault.
Come on, let's just
talk tomorrow
when you're okay already.
- Joahae...
- Good night.
Good night.
Joahae, joahae...
Joahae...
Go to sleep, okay?
What is it with that joahae?
Joahae...
- Joahae...
- Good night already, Jin Ho.
Joahae...
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
This is the friend of Jin Ho
I was telling you about.
There.
Hey, it's Boss Idol!
Hey.
Guys, it's Boss Idol.
- Hey, Boss Idol!
- Boss Idol!
- Boss!
- Hello, hello.
You ended up here, Boss.
Ah, well, I just wanted to talk
to the owner.
Is there a problem?
- [INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Nothing really,
Peter just recommended
so I wanted to present
my business proposal.
They barely come here anymore
though.
Just leave your number,
and I'll pass it on to them.
All right.
Here.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
We're already searching for Jin
Ho's friend,
but it looks like they've gone
underground.
I think, Berdugo,
they were warned or maybe they
sensed something.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
I don't need explanations.
- I need results!
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Because if that Jin Ho talks
and points at me,
I'll cut your head off!
You know I dont make
empty threats, Liza.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hurry up!
I understand, Berdugo.
All right,
get out of here already!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KNOCKING]
Go home first!
Why?
What about you?
I'll wait here.
Right here?
Didn't they say the owners
don't come here anymore?
But there's an anniversary
event, right?
Then obviously,
it's impossible for the owners
not to show up there.
That's why I need
to be here early
so I can meet them first.
Hey...
Fine, if you're going to wait...
What now?
Then I'll wait too.
You're so stubborn.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
It's peaceful here, right?
Yeah.
Makes me not want to leave
this place anymore.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Good thing you're feeling
better now.
Thanks to you.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Joey!
Andrew?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
What are you doing here?
Joey, I'm sorry,
but I can't stay silent anymore.
I love you.
Andrew...
I waited so long to hear
you say that.
You already pushed her away.
If you do it again,
I won't stop her
from choosing me.
That won't happen again.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey.
I felt that, huh.
- Felt what?
- [STAMMERS]
What are you even
I felt you doing something,
hugging me, touching my cheek.
- I saw that, okay?
- You're disgusting, boy!
- You were caressing my cheek.
- [CHUCKLES]
- What are you even saying?
And I'm the disgusting one, huh.
So that's why you don't like
Joey because you're confused?
You're disgusting.
What are you talking about?
[LAUGHS]
It's okay, I understand.
It's okay.
You already pushed her away.
If you do it again,
I won't stop her
from choosing me.
That can't happen.
Peter, we need to find Joey
before it's too late.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Who's that?
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hey, hey, hey...
Wait, isn't she the owner?
Isn't that her?
- What?
- Yeah, I think that's Eun Ji.
Come on, let's go to him.
[CLATTERING IN DISTANCE]
[GROANS]
[PLEASANT MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, Jin Ho,
you're awake already!
- Good morning!
- Good morning.
Looks like you're feeling
better now, huh?
Yeah, I feel much better now.
That's good.
You know, good thing
you stocked up on antibiotics.
I stocked up everything
I might need.
Ah, that's wise!
- You fetched water?
- [♪PLEASANT MUSIC PLAYING♪]
Yup!
Well, you might need it right
away.
And not just one,
not just two,
but three pails of water.
But one of them is just for me.
Don't touch that one, okay?
Thank you, Joey.
Oh, it's nothing.
Friends take care
of each other, right?
[PLEASANT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Oh, by the way.
You never mentioned
that you drank alcohol
before taking your medicine
last night.
You ended up saying all sorts
of things over and over.
You were acting crazy.
What do you mean?
No, because you kept repeating
something last night,
it's...
Joahae?
What's that?
[LIGHT PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Ah...
Joahae...
That means is...
Ah...
Thank you.
- Yeah, thank you.
- Ah...
So it means thank you.
I thought it was something else.
You kept saying it over
and over.
No, that's just thank you.
Well...
I should actually be
the one saying that
because I still haven't
thanked you
for saving me from Liza.
So thank you, okay?
I mean...
Joahae, Jin Ho.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Yeah, you're welcome.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Let's eat, come on.
Ah... This is really good, huh.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Coffee?
No, thanks.
[SIGHS IN RELIEF]
It's beautiful here, right?
You never get tired
of looking at it.
I know.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
You know, you should've just
stayed here after you left.
Then maybe you wouldn't have
gone back to Liza.
I know you two have history,
but you get it.
Of course,
your life here would've been
much more peaceful, right?
You're right, Joey.
I wanna apologize.
I really used you before
just to find Theresa.
That's Liza's real name.
And...
I'm not a real agent, Joey.
I was with a bad group
back in Korea.
Theresa and I...
We were together.
We had a plan.
Own enough money,
then disappear somewhere quiet
and start over.
But...
She had bigger dreams.
Let me guess,
for her drug empire?
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Unbelievable.
Even I struggle just handling
my social media pages.
When I found out again,
I thought I could remind her
of the peaceful life we wanted,
but, she's not
that person anymore.
She is really ambitious.
Well...
there's nothing wrong
with being ambitious.
The problem is, the kind
of ambition she chose
destroys families and ruins
people's lives.
And to be honest...
You know, being with you guys,
laughing, arguing,
protecting each other,
I think that's the life
I want now.
That life really suits you
better anyway,
being a saviour and a protector.
Really?
Mmm-hmm.
I can't even count
how many times you've saved me
already.
The bottom line is,
you always choose
to do what's right
because you're a good person.
You're a good person, Jin Ho.
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hurry up already!
We're starting at 12 noon!
Guys, fix the seating already!
Oh, hello!
Yes, welcome!
Quick, quick!
Hurry up!
Hurry!
Fix the chairs!
Excuse me.
Are you Eun Ji?
Ah, I know you!
Yeah.
Weren't we the ones
who defended you
from the people
you owed money to?
- You're running away from us?
- Sir!
Please help me!
This person owes us
a lot of money.
[THUDS]
- Maybe that's Eman Pacquiao.
- [INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Eman Pacquiao?
You said before that since
we saved you,
you wouldn't lie to us.
Okay, we're here because we're
looking for Jin Ho.
Do you know where he is?
I don't know.
I do not see him.
Sorry, sorry.
But you know where he might've
gone, right?
No, I don't know.
Sorry, sorry.
Ah, no, no Tagalog.
Only little English, okay?
Busy, busy! Sorry, sorry!
Bye!
[SHOUTS IN KOREAN]
That punk.
Before, he used to speak Tagalog
so fluently.
I'm sure he knows where Jin Ho
is.
But he definitely won't talk.
[SIGHS IN RELIEF]
[SPEAKING IN KOREAN]
What did you say?
- Nothing.
- Ah.
I know you want to go home
already.
I was just, ah,
letting a little time pass.
Just make sure it's safe,
and I will take you back
to your family.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Really?
Thank you, Jin Ho.
I just need to take care
of few things first.
Okay?
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE KEYS CLICKING]
[RINGING]
Hurry up, hurry up.
Get the things from the car.
Our guests are waiting.
[PHONE RINGS]
[SPEAKS IN KOREAN]
Jin Ho?
Eun Ji...
[SPEAKING IN KOREAN]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SIGHS]
[SPEAKING IN KOREAN]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[REVVING]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Come on, hurry up, hurry up!
[CAR CHIMES]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[REVVING]
It's been 2 days already,
Miguel.
We should've found Joey by now.
We'll find her.
I'll bring Joey back here.
And we'll return this to her.
[PHONE RINGING]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Hello, Peter?
Uncle...
Uncle, we're following Jin Ho's
friend right now.
- Friend?
- Yes, a friend.
His business partner.
Looks like he's the one who'll
lead us to Jin Ho.
Where are you?
I'll follow.
In Sta. Monica,
at the small town there.
Copy, we're on our way.
[GUN COCKS]
We are switching vehicles
because the police and media,
they are probably looking
for my car.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
And once I drop you off
at your house,
I have to leave immediately.
Right away?
Why?
Because your father
might arrest me.
No, he won't do that.
I'll talk to him.
I'll explain everything to him.
I'll fix all of this.
That's a promise, Jin Ho.
[SIGHS]
[SPEAKS IN KOREAN]
Huh?
- What was that?
- [PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
Eun Ji?
- Okay.
- [STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
He's here.
Let's go.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE RINGING]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
This better be good.
We already know the location.
We're heading there now to
capture Jin Ho
and the beloved daughter
of Miguel Delgado.
Good.
You know, I realized something.
We'll finally silence Jin Ho,
and at the same time,
get revenge on that Delgado
through her beloved daughter.
Two birds with one stone.
That's efficient revenge, Liza.
Now finish them off.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
They're about to escape.
Finish them off, Matias!
- Hide!
- [POLICE SIREN WAILING]
Kang Dae-Hyun,
you're under arrest!
I'll fix all of this.
That person should
never be trusted!
What were you thinking?
When I say I'll get revenge,
- I'll get revenge!
- [GUN FIRING]
I won't stop until that cursed
syndicate is gone,
especially their leader,
Berdugo.
If I were the leader of that
syndicate,
I probably would've had you
killed too!